Sephiroth by MGSSJ2 and MattFV
-------------------------------------

After... 4 years? I've finally finished this f*cking char xD. It was supposed to be
released together with Cloud, but eh... I left Mugen for a couple of years and then I had
so many ideas of stuff to do with this char, that it took me more than a year to finish
it DX but anyways, we finally got it :D
The size of this character is astronomical, going for a lot more than Sasuke Fuga, and though
the contents are not as many, the epicness of the character will hopefully make up for it :)


Credits
-------
- Credits for the original spriter, BraveShyGuy, and even more credits to my close friend
MattFV, the best spriter and friend I've had the pleasure to work with :)
- All my supporters in Youtube and other Mugen forums, you're the ones that keep me
going even after all this time :)

Movelist
--------
(all magics, Limit Breaks and specials can be chained with normal combos)

Basicals:
Air Dash: F,F (in air)
A and B: basic combos.
Uppercut: A/B while holding down (chainable)
A and B: aerial combos.
Counter: X.
Charge: Y.

Magics:
(all with level 1 or 1.5 bar)

Flare: D,DF,F,x.
Freeze: D,DF,F,y.
Thunder: D,DF,F,z.
Wall: D,DF,B,x.
Tornado: D,DF,B,y.
Bio: D,DF,B,z.

Specials:
Heaven's Light: B,F,c (also in air)
Pale Horse: B,F,z.

Limit Breaks:
Energy Waves: D,F,a. (level 1 bar) (additional hit with a/b after finished) 
Octaslash: D,B,a. (level 1.5 bar)
Hell's Gate: D,F,b. (level 2 bar)
Shadow Flare: D,B,b (level 2.5 bar)
Oblivion: D,F,c. (level 3 bar)
Heartless Angel: D,B,c. (level 2.5 bar) (takes a lot of time to cast, but decreases
opponent's HP to 1)

Hypers:
Comet2 (or Meteor): D,F,x+y (level 3 bar)
Supernova: D,F,a+b (level 3 bar, takes a little to cast, can only be done after 30 in-game secs)
Black Materia - Meteor: c+z (level 3 bar, also takes a little to cast, can only be done with 25% HP or less)


FAQ:

Q: so what are you gonna code now?
A: I have a few projects to do with MattFV, keep up to date with them in my Youtube channel :) 

Q: what about Naruto characters? Are you gonna do any of them ever again?
A: probably not... there are already enough Naruto coders, and I prefer to do characters that have not been properly made in Mugen.

Q: Seph is doing really annoying stuff and I can't beat him! What do I do?
A: Seph doesn't like you messing up with his data...

Q: where can I find all of your creations?
A: on the Internet! Now seriously, I'm aware that most of my characters' links are down, but I'll eventually take the time to do a Drive folder or something where all my creations can be downloaded. Just give me some time :P but all my older stuff should be mirrored somewhere else in the Internet. Google is your friend :)

Q: can you help me with a certain project? Where can I contact you?
A: in my Youtube channel. Just message me and I'll probably answer you right away. For projects it depends on the interest I have on it, but contact me and I'll check any offers out :)




That's all I think. I hope you enjoy this character as much as I enjoyed coding it! And let's all wait for that beautiful remake soon :')
Goodbye!

MGSSJ2
http://www.youtube.com/user/MGSSJ2